Guide to the Elliot Glass and Ken Marsh Video Collection MSS.334
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Music At The Joyous Lake, 1975; 334.0223 (Box 12, Reel 334.0223)
- Ballet Of Belief, 1973; 334.0224 (Box 12, Reel 334.0224)
- Base V. Aug 11, 75., 1975-08-15; 334.0225 (Box 12, Reel 334.0225)
- I-Dodge, undated; 334.0226 (Box 12, Reel 334.0226)
- New American Mime Co., 1972; 334.0227 (Box 12, Reel 334.0227)
- Memorial Day Parade, 1976; 334.0228 (Box 12, Reel 334.0228)
- Weather-Winter 2, undated; 334.0229 (Box 12, Reel 334.0229)
- Meet The Family, 1974; 334.0230 (Box 12, Reel 334.0230)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video, Duration: 12min., Reel Size: 5"
- Catskill Game Farm, 1972; 334.0231 (Box 12, Reel 334.0231)
- Base-Mancusso, 1975; 334.0232 (Box 12, Reel 334.0232)
- Muppets, undated; 334.0233 (Box 12, Reel 334.0233)
- Ecohomo II, undated; 334.0234 (Box 12, Reel 334.0234)
- Vasulkas II, undated; 334.0235 (Box 12, Reel 334.0235)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0236 (Box 12, Reel 334.0236)
- Weather-Summer, undated; 334.0237 (Box 12, Reel 334.0237)
- Woodstock Music Coop, undated; 334.0238 (Box 12, Reel 334.0238)
- Weather-Interview, undated; 334.0239 (Box 12, Reel 334.0239)
- Harvey Fite, 1975-10-16; 334.0240 (Box 12, Reel 334.0240)
- WCV Community Video Sampler, 1973; 334.0241 (Box 12, Reel 334.0241)
- Harvey Fite, 1976; 334.0242 (Box 12, Reel 334.0242)
- Lenox Girls- Montreal, undated; 334.0243 (Box 12, Reel 334.0243)
- The Muppets With Arlo Guthrie, 1979-10-29; 334.0244 (Box 12, Reel 334.0244)
- Magic Marnie day 1 + 2 July 5-6, undated; 334.0245 (Box 13, Reel 334.0245)
- Passive Solar Energy, 1975-01-01; 334.0246 (Box 13, Reel 334.0246)
- Mein Sheyn Kinder, 1976; 334.0247 (Box 13, Reel 334.0247)
- Spider Webb: Tattoo Artist, 1976; 334.0248 (Box 13, Reel 334.0248)
- Conversation with H. H. Channer, 1973; 334.0249 (Box 13, Reel 334.0249)
- Off-Air Edit and Synergism, 1975; 334.0250 (Box 13, Reel 334.0250)
- Baby, 1975; 334.0251 (Box 13, Reel 334.0251)
- Bass Color II, undated; 334.0252 (Box 13, Reel 334.0252)
- Trent, undated; 334.0253 (Box 13, Reel 334.0253)
- Weather-Winter, undated; 334.0254 (Box 13, Reel 334.0254)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Dub], Duration: 30min., Reel Size: 5"
- [untitled], undated; 334.0255 (Box 13, Reel 334.0255)
- School Feeding Program, 1975; 334.0256 (Box 13, Reel 334.0256)
- Video For WBAI Benefit, 1973; 334.0257 (Box 13, Reel 334.0257)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video, Duration: 29min., Reel Size: 5"
- Lenox girl, undated; 334.0258 (Box 13, Reel 334.0258)
- Reale - AA, undated; 334.0259 (Box 13, Reel 334.0259)
- Heart screening, undated; 334.0260 (Box 13, Reel 334.0260)
- WCV Magazine # II, 1972-02-17; 334.0261 (Box 13, Reel 334.0261)
- Drive thru Wdstk Sat Jan 10, '76, 1976-01-10; 334.0262 (Box 13, Reel 334.0262)
- Rebecca's Spider, 1975-06-15; 334.0263 (Box 13, Reel 334.0263)
- The Ball of Redemption, undated; 334.0264 (Box 13, Reel 334.0264)
- Titles-Lab credit, undated; 334.0265 (Box 13, Reel 334.0265)
- Light Matrix, undated; 334.0266 (Box 13, Reel 334.0266)
- Clarence Schmidt I, 1971; 334.0267 (Box 13, Reel 334.0267)
- Weather-Fall, undated; 334.0268 (Box 13, Reel 334.0268)
- Women's Lib vs Construction Worker, 1970; 334.0269 (Box 14, Reel 334.0269)
- Osebo's Drum, 1976-08-01; 334.0270 (Box 14, Reel 334.0270)
- Leon Barzin + Lucille Blanch, 1976-05-13; 334.0271 (Box 14, Reel 334.0271)
- Watergate, undated; 334.0272 (Box 14, Reel 334.0272)
- Eddie Hicks Cutting Side 1, undated; 334.0273 (Box 14, Reel 334.0273)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Master Edit], Duration: 30min., Reel Size: 5"
- [untitled], undated; 334.0274 (Box 14, Reel 334.0274)
- Aileen Cramer, 1978-12-09; 334.0275 (Box 14, Reel 334.0275)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0276 (Box 14, Reel 334.0276)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0277 (Box 14, Reel 334.0277)
- Bass-Color I, undated; 334.0278 (Box 14, Reel 334.0278)
- Weather NYSCA submission, undated; 334.0279 (Box 14, Reel 334.0279)
- Associate Artists Program NYSCA Proposal, 1978; 334.0280 (Box 14, Reel 334.0280)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0281 (Box 14, Reel 334.0281)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0282 (Box 14, Reel 334.0282)
- Flood Water, 1973-12-20; 334.0283 (Box 14, Reel 334.0283)
- Mancusso II, undated; 334.0284 (Box 14, Reel 334.0284)
- Wild Herb + Plants of Wdstck, undated; 334.0285 (Box 14, Reel 334.0285)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Edit], Duration: 23min., Reel Size: 5"
- Lenox Girls, undated; 334.0286 (Box 14, Reel 334.0286)
- Wdstck Mem day Parade 76, 1976; 334.0287 (Box 14, Reel 334.0287)
- Artists TV Lab Sampler, 1975; 334.0288 (Box 14, Reel 334.0288)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0289 (Box 14, Reel 334.0289)
- Lenox Girls, undated; 334.0290 (Box 14, Reel 334.0290)
- Elaine Pregnancy, 1974-11-01; 334.0291 (Box 14, Reel 334.0291)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0292 (Box 14, Reel 334.0292)
- Ron Hay Video Work, 1976; 334.0293 (Box 15, Reel 334.0293)
- Winter/Weather I, undated; 334.0294 (Box 15, Reel 334.0294)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video, Duration: 5min., Reel Size: 5"
- Bass I, undated; 334.0295 (Box 15, Reel 334.0295)
- June 1, 1979 I, 1979-06-01; 334.0296 (Box 15, Reel 334.0296)
- Journey on Horseback, 1974; 334.0297 (Box 15, Reel 334.0297)
- Jane Roberts: Seth Speaks, 1973; 334.0298 (Box 15, Reel 334.0298)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0299 (Box 15, Reel 334.0299)
- Conversations w/ George Numrich, 1973; 334.0300 (Box 15, Reel 334.0300)
- Artists TV Lab Sampler, 1976; 334.0301 (Box 15, Reel 334.0301)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0302 (Box 15, Reel 334.0302)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0303 (Box 15, Reel 334.0303)
- Harvey Fite 10), 1976-02-19; 334.0304 (Box 15, Reel 334.0304)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Original], Duration: 15min., Reel Size: 5"
- Harvey Fite 11), 1976-02-26; 334.0305 (Box 15, Reel 334.0305)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Original], Duration: 20min., Reel Size: 5"
- Harvey Fite 9), 1976-02-19; 334.0306 (Box 15, Reel 334.0306)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Original], Duration: 30min., Reel Size: 5"
- Harvey Fite 3), 1975-10-12; 334.0307 (Box 15, Reel 334.0307)
- Harvey Fite 5), 1975-10-16; 334.0308 (Box 15, Reel 334.0308)
- Harvey Fite 13), 1976; 334.0309 (Box 15, Reel 334.0309)
- Harvey Fite 7), 1976-01-27; 334.0310 (Box 15, Reel 334.0310)
- Harvey Fite 8), 1976-02-19; 334.0311 (Box 15, Reel 334.0311)
- Harvey Fite 12), 1976-02-26; 334.0312 (Box 15, Reel 334.0312)
- Harvey Fite 1), 1972-08; 334.0313 (Box 15, Reel 334.0313)
- Harvey Fite 2), 1975-08-20; 334.0314 (Box 15, Reel 334.0314)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Original], Duration: 25min., Reel Size: 5"
- Harvey Fite 6), 1976-01-27; 334.0315 (Box 15, Reel 334.0315)
- Don Cherry, undated; 334.0316 (Box 16, Reel 334.0316)
- Lenox R IB, undated; 334.0317 (Box 16, Reel 334.0317)
- Earth Pulse and Embryonics 6 1/2, 1975; 334.0318 (Box 16, Reel 334.0318)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video, Duration: 16min., Reel Size: 5"
- Reservoir Drive, 1976; 334.0319 (Box 16, Reel 334.0319)
- III Dodge, undated; 334.0320 (Box 16, Reel 334.0320)
- The Sugar Tree, 1978; 334.0321 (Box 16, Reel 334.0321)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0322 (Box 16, Reel 334.0322)
- Valma's Brthday Voyage, undated; 334.0323 (Box 16, Reel 334.0323)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Edit], Duration: 30min., Reel Size: 5"
- Community Video Interview, 1976-07-15; 334.0324 (Box 16, Reel 334.0324)
- Chedabel I, undated; 334.0325 (Box 16, Reel 334.0325)
- Chedabel II, undated; 334.0326 (Box 16, Reel 334.0326)
- Chedabel III, undated; 334.0327 (Box 16, Reel 334.0327)
- Bass III, 1975-07-03; 334.0328 (Box 16, Reel 334.0328)
- Burn Again Poly, undated; 334.0329 (Box 16, Reel 334.0329)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0330 (Box 16, Reel 334.0330)
- Parade Weather, undated; 334.0331 (Box 16, Reel 334.0331)
- Feeding the Elderly, 1974; 334.0332 (Box 16, Reel 334.0332)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Dub], Duration: 15min., Reel Size: 5"
- Joyous Lake, undated; 334.0333 (Box 16, Reel 334.0333)
- Poetry at the Lab, 1978-06-01; 334.0334 (Box 16, Reel 334.0334)
- Granger- 3 shorts, undated; 334.0335 (Box 16, Reel 334.0335)
- On Drugs and Born in a Prison, 1977; 334.0336 (Box 16, Reel 334.0336)
- Traver Hollow Bridge, undated; 334.0337 (Box 16, Reel 334.0337)
- Weather - Spring Masher 22-36 (2), undated; 334.0338 (Box 17, Reel 334.0338)
- What Do You Do For Pain? B/W WCV/Marsh/Forno 1975, 334.0339 (Box 17, Reel 334.0339)
- Weather - Winter Master 1-11(13) (1), undated; 334.0340 (Box 17, Reel 334.0340)
- Aug 71 Woodstock WCV-KM, 1971-08-01; 334.0341 (Box 17, Reel 334.0341)
- WCV- 8/30/72 Reel 2 Fire Gladstone, 1972-08-30; 334.0342 (Box 17, Reel 334.0342)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0343 (Box 17, Reel 334.0343)
- Intro to Vegetarian Cooking B. Friedlander Edit 25 min. Colorized, undated; 334.0344 (Box 17, Reel 334.0344)
- Goullas, undated; 334.0345 (Box 17, Reel 334.0345)
- Road Kills 19 min. Color, No Nukes: Seabrook 1976 12 min Color Star Route, Willow, NY 12495, 334.0346 (Box 17, Reel 334.0346)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video, Duration: 28min., Reel Size: 5"
- Copy of Gazette 2, undated; 334.0347 (Box 17, Reel 334.0347)
- Opus 40 1 Music Dance, undated; 334.0348 (Box 17, Reel 334.0348)
- Robot Audio, undated; 334.0349 (Box 17, Reel 334.0349)
  Format: 1/4 Open Reel Audio, Duration: 30min., Reel Size: 5"
- Daughters on Mothers 30 min B/W, undated; 334.0350 (Box 17, Reel 334.0350)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0351 (Box 17, Reel 334.0351)
- The Bass II - Initial Wrap - start of carving I - July 29 - 75, 1975-07-21; 334.0352 (Box 17, Reel 334.0352)
- Poetry at Lab 2-Camilla Norris - Peyton Houston, undated; 334.0353 (Box 17, Reel 334.0353)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0354 (Box 17, Reel 334.0354)
- Bass VI, undated; 334.0355 (Box 17, Reel 334.0355)
- Trees, undated; 334.0356 (Box 17, Reel 334.0356)
- June 1, 1979 23rd St II, 1979-06-01; 334.0357 (Box 17, Reel 334.0357)
- Act at WCV Show, undated; 334.0358 (Box 17, Reel 334.0358)
- A.A - FACCI, undated; 334.0359 (Box 17, Reel 334.0359)
- Vision #2 - Frost/Vision Rubin Commentary, undated; 334.0360 (Box 17, Reel 334.0360)
- Eddie Hicks/Rondi Sound B/W in Studio, undated; 334.0361 (Box 18, Reel 334.0361)
- Weather - World Weather Blds. 1. Visuals of Satellite Station 2. Begin int w/ late, undated; 334.0362 (Box 18, Reel 334.0362)
- Barbara Fite Sept. 78, undated; 334.0363 (Box 18, Reel 334.0363)
- Toward Tomorrow Phil Demetrion 7/77, 1977-07; 334.0364 (Box 18, Reel 334.0364)
- Kathleen Spivack: Morning Is My Best Time, Keeler/Rotko color, undated; 334.0365 (Box 18, Reel 334.0365)
- Tom Penning - Harvey Fite Sept 7, 1978, undated; 334.0366 (Box 18, Reel 334.0366)
- Audio only - Lenox girls on men, undated; 334.0367 (Box 18, Reel 334.0367)
- The Muppets; Dudley Moore October 22, 1979, undated; 334.0368 (Box 18, Reel 334.0368)
- Eddie Hicks I June 9, 79 Rondi Sound, undated; 334.0369 (Box 18, Reel 334.0369)
- Dean and Dudley Rain Dance Terra Firma + Man 23" Man 11/13/71, undated; 334.0370 (Box 18, Reel 334.0370)
- Tom Beshaw ATT Oct 12, 78 II, undated; 334.0371 (Box 18, Reel 334.0371)
- Lenox Girls Wash. Sq. Pk., undated; 334.0372 (Box 18, Reel 334.0372)
- Dubos Ecology, undated; 334.0373 (Box 18, Reel 334.0373)
- Women Survey Supermarket '71 CV, undated; 334.0374 (Box 18, Reel 334.0374)
- CAT CV Edit, undated; 334.0375 (Box 18, Reel 334.0375)
- Video Experiment: Charlie - Music Abstract Lord Rusty Rap + Charlie = Porno Movie Clip, undated; 334.0376 (Box 18, Reel 334.0376)
- Tall Oak, undated; 334.0377 (Box 18, Reel 334.0377)
- Randall's Island, undated; 334.0378 (Box 18, Reel 334.0378)
- Gay Lib Forum V, undated; 334.0379 (Box 18, Reel 334.0379)
- Indian Thanksgiving Plymouth Rock 1970 People's, undated; 334.0380 (Box 18, Reel 334.0380)
- AV Young Lords - Church Takeover - 10/70 Jail's Press Conference - 1/71, undated; 334.0381 (Box 18, Reel 334.0381)
- AV Copy of P.R., INA, People's Video Theatre, undated; 334.0382 (Box 18, Reel 334.0382)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Copy], Duration: 20min., Reel Size: 4.5"
- [untitled], undated; 334.0383 (Box 18, Reel 334.0383)
- Zubin's "Fashion in Living Art", 1975; 334.0384 (Box 19, Reel 334.0384)
- Wolfgang Stoerchle, 1970; 334.0385 (Box 19, Reel 334.0385)
- VTR - Video Gallery #2, 1976; 334.0386 (Box 19, Reel 334.0386)
- Videographics for Winberg Bass, 1972; 334.0387 (Box 19, Reel 334.0387)
- Eat With Taste - Kate Parker, 1977; 334.0388 (Box 19, Reel 334.0388)
- Hindustan III - Eric Segal (sp?), 1973; 334.0389 (Box 19, Reel 334.0389)
- News Spoof - Harvard - Al Franken?, 1973; 334.0390 (Box 19, Reel 334.0390)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0391 (Box 19, Reel 334.0391)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0392 (Box 19, Reel 334.0392)
- VTR - Video Gallery #1, 1976; 334.0393 (Box 19, Reel 334.0393)
- Jane Roberrts: Seth Speaks - H. Channer, 1973; 334.0394 (Box 19, Reel 334.0394)
- Catskill Game Farm II - WCV Staff, 1972; 334.0395 (Box 19, Reel 334.0395)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0396 (Box 19, Reel 334.0396)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0397 (Box 19, Reel 334.0397)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0398 (Box 19, Reel 334.0398)
- Out of Context - Milosh/Holtzman/Marsh/Holtzman, 1973; 334.0399 (Box 19, Reel 334.0399)
- Weather - Spring Masher, undated; 334.0400 (Box 19, Reel 334.0400)
- Weather - Summer Masher, undated; 334.0401 (Box 19, Reel 334.0401)
- Woodstock is Only A Town - Keeler/Rotko/Arlin, 1974; 334.0402 (Box 19, Reel 334.0402)
- Hindustan - Eric Segal, 1973; 334.0403 (Box 19, Reel 334.0403)
  Format: 1/2 Open Reel Video [Edit Copy], Duration: 30min., Reel Size: 5"
- Lions Paper Drive, undated; 334.0404 (Box 19, Reel 334.0404)
- [untitled], undated; 334.0405 (Box 19, Reel 334.0405)